

Gonzalo, TERZANO

Web Developer
26 Years
Córdoba, Argentina
Mobile: +549 0264 154649709
E-mail: gonzaloterzano@gmail.com

PERSONAL STATEMENT

Hello! My name is Gonzalo Terzano. I am a Semi-Senior Web Developer, with 3-4 years of experience in the area. I have many skills to work as a team member and also individually. I always push myself to the limit in order to achieve excellence in my work.

EXPERIENCE

February 2017 – Present McAfee *Cordoba, Argentina*

Position: Software Engineer

Working on a huge project focused on the security of big companies and government institutions, with excellent professional opportunities.

February 2016 – Present Globant Cordoba, Argentina

Position: Web UI Developer

I worked in a busy team, sometimes under pressure. Always making projects of eLearning, mostly using AngularJS, but also creating friendly & interactive environments with HTML5 and Phaser (JS Framework).

April 2015 – January 2016 TravelPAQ San Juan, Argentina

Position: Web UI Developer & Backend Developer

I worked in a startup focused on improve relationships between tourism companies. This was an exciting experience where I learned a lot of new and different technologies.

April 2010 – January 2016 UNSJ, FCEFyN

San Juan, Argentina

Position: Teaching assistant

Worked in six different subjects, assisting in practical classes, even giving class in some particular cases.

SKILLS

✓ AngularJS
 ✓ Bootstrap
 ✓ PHP
 ✓ JQuery
 ✓ CakePHP
 ✓ C#
 ✓ Git
 ✓ C

✓ KnockoutJS
 ✓ Gulp
 ✓ HTML5
 ✓ NodeJS
 ✓ Photoshop
 ✓ CSS3
 ✓ Jira

EDUCATION

2009 - Present "Degree in Computer Science"

San Juan - Argentina UNSJ - Fac. Cs. Exactas F. y N., without

preseting the Thesis.

GPA: 8.6 of 10

2005 - 2008 "Electronics Technician"

San Juan - Argentina UNSJ - Esc Industrial D. F. Sarmiento

GPA: 8.57 of 10

LENGUAGES

Spanish: Native

English: Conversational level